Okay, so let's just clean up
Được rồi, hãy dọn dẹp
this entire section.
toàn bộ phần này.
So for this I'm gonna go to Action on my file system
Tôi sẽ vào Action trên file system
and delete it, and for this I have to enter
và xóa nó, phải nhập
the file system ID, so I'll just copy and paste this.
ID file system, tôi sẽ copy và dán.
And so okay, we're gonna get rid of our file system.
Được rồi, chúng ta sẽ xóa file system.
Perfect!
Hoàn hảo!
Now into our EC2 instances, make sure to terminate
Giờ vào EC2 instances, nhớ terminate
any running EC2 instance, so that's good.
mọi EC2 instance đang chạy, như vậy là xong.
Then in terms of volumes, we're going to have to
Tiếp theo với volumes, chúng ta cần
clear up volumes as well, so any volumes that is available
dọn các volume còn lại, bất kỳ volume nào đang available
you have to terminate it, so I'll right-click
bạn phải xóa, tôi sẽ right-click
and delete all these volumes.
và delete tất cả các volume này.
Okay.
Được rồi.
Now for snapshots, you've made a few snapshots,
Tiếp theo, bạn đã tạo vài snapshot,
so let's just go back and delete every snapshot you have.
hãy quay lại và xóa mọi snapshot.
Just so that you can get rid
Để bạn có thể loại bỏ
and not pay for any storage for snapshots.
và không phải trả tiền lưu trữ cho snapshot.
Okay.
Được rồi.
And then finally, security groups.
Cuối cùng là security group.
If you want to, because it's going to get a lot of
Nếu bạn muốn, vì sẽ có rất nhiều
security groups right here,
security group ở đây,
you can basically delete so many of these security groups
bạn có thể xóa bớt nhiều security group
except the one for default, so just don't delete that one.
trừ cái default, đừng xóa nó.
So you can go ahead and delete these security groups.
Vì vậy bạn có thể xóa các security group này.
And they will only be deleted once you have, basically,
Chúng chỉ bị xóa sau khi bạn
deleted all your EC2 instances associated with those.
xóa mọi EC2 instance liên quan.
So maybe these won't be deleted right away
Có thể chúng không bị xóa ngay
but you can just keep on trying until it works.
nhưng cứ thử lại cho đến khi được.
So I'll delete this security group now.
Tôi sẽ xóa security group này.
Yes this one works.
Vâng, cái này đã xóa.
I'll delete the load balancer for the security group.
Tôi sẽ xóa security group của load balancer.
Yes that worked, and this EC2 for EFS,
Được rồi, và security group EC2 cho EFS này
it's still used by my instances
vẫn đang được dùng bởi các instance
so I have to wait for my instances
nên tôi phải đợi các instance
to be shutting down properly before I can go ahead
tắt hẳn trước khi
and delete that last security group.
xóa security group cuối cùng.
So I'll have to wait a little bit, but that's it.
Tôi sẽ phải chờ một chút, vậy thôi.
Once you've cleared up everything
Khi đã dọn xong mọi thứ
you're ready to go for the next section.
bạn sẵn sàng cho phần tiếp theo.